Contact

hmatejowsky@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/matejowsky-haley-037092107 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Emergency Medicine Nursing CPR Certified

Languages

English

Certifications

Transplant Nursing Certification
Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN)

Honors-Awards

Deans List

Matejowsky Haley

RN at Ben Taub Hospital Emergency Room. Licensed Paramedic at Angleton Area Emergency Medical Services

Galveston, Texas

Summary

I am an energetic and hardworking person with a positive attitude. I have been a licensed paramedic for 2 years and am currently about to finish my Bachelor of Nursing at The University of Texas Medical Branch this December. I am looking to work in an ICU or ER setting where I will be able to master my skills and become a proficient nurse.

Experience

Ben Taub General Hospital Registered Nurse

Angleton Area Emergency Medical Services Licensed Paramedic February 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Target Phamacy
Pharmacy Technician
April 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 5 months)

Target

Guest Service Associate
August 2009 - April 2013 (3 years 9 months)

I made daily break schedules for the cashiers and guest service employees as well as found coverage for any call ins. I also managed any problems that any guests may have had that day.

Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Bachelor of Applied Science (BASc), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Blinn College

Associate's Degree, Emergency Medical Technology/Technician (EMT Paramedic) · (2010 - 2012)